

BENJAMIN SOLT

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

SUMMARY

Full Stack Engineer who is eager to grow and learn new programs.

Prior experience includes 10 years in retail, developing skills in teamwork, communication, and customer service.

In addition have Bachelors of Science took initiative, self taught Epic Games, Unreal Engine creating games.

SKILLS

- CSS
- HTML
- JavaScript
- React
- Redux
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Unreal Engine
- 3D Studio Max
- Python

EDUCATION

LAMBDA SCHOOL - REMOTE

July 2019 - Present Full Stack Web Developer

TEMPLE UNIVERSITY CERTIFICATION IN WEBSITE DESIGN

May 2012

- Intensive course focused on creative web design
- page layouts and art assets
- Utilized HTML, CSS and Dreamweaver

THE ART INSTITUTE OF PHILADELPHIA

December 2007

• Bachelor of Science Degree in Media Arts and Animation

CONTACT INFO

- Bensolt@gmail.com
- Cell: 215 360 5410
- Fort Washington, PA
- Bensolt.com
- LinkedIn
- Github

PROJECTS

PORTFOLIO

April 2020 - Present Built to showcase personal projects. HTML/CSS | JavaScript | React

GROA

Feb 17 2020, 8 weeks

Built to recommend movies to user, based on how user rates movies HTML/CSS | JavaScript | React | AWS

- As Front End Developer built Authorization, Login, display layout of movie info
- Solved problems and trouble shot bugs with team members
- Collaborated remotely with team of 6 web developers, 2 data science, and 1 UX designer

EXPERIENCE

FRESH MARKET

HORSHAM, PA

AUGUST 2016 - JUNE 2019

GIANT GROCERY STORE

WILLOW GROVE, PA

NOVEMBER 2013 - AUGUST 2016

- Produce Associate
- Restock produce and ensure available products are fresh daily
- Respond to shopper inquiries, assist with locating specific products and provide overall friendly customer service